Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Yay!
Happy Birthday!
Is it started?
Hello everyone!
Yoo-hoo!
Yay!
So, this is the camera for the fan club.
We're also doing a fan club streaming at the same time!
Please check it out!
Please watch it!
So, I guess it's YouTube?
So, I, Hiyori Yoshikawa, turned 22 years old today, August 12!
Congratulations!
Good morning.
Thank you very much.
Yes, well,
Today,
Oh, I fell.
Don't look.
Don't look at that.
Okay, so...,Yes, that's right,
Today, Oharu will be
Today is the first day of the performance.
The show is starting today,
Oharu is on leave,
There he is!
There she is!
Waru-chan was there!
Isn't she cute?
She's kind of cheering me on in her pose.
Like, congratulations.
What?
I wanted to congratulate you.
Bad!
Waru!
Waru, why, we're almost there, aren't we?
It's okay!
Hang on!
Hang in there!
Thanks, man.
So it looks like Awahada is watching me too, so I'll put your mind at ease.
Oh, there he is. He said, "I'm here!
Congratulations.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
You're having fun, congratulations.
Good luck.Good luck.
Good luck.
Thank you.
So, let's take a look at today's lineup.
Ta-da!
Hiyoni Yoshikawa Birthday Party Live Streaming
(1) Birthday party for everyone!
Please prepare cake and juice.
Yay!
I hope everyone is ready today.
How's it going?
But some of you already did.
Some of you have already prepared.
Oh, yeah.
The tweeters.
Twitter.
Tweet a lot.
Extra.
How do you say "extra" tweets?
Oh, I don't know.
Extra.
That's right.
Something like that.
X, it's kind of an X in the name.
What is it?
Yes. So, should I say all of this?
Number 2, 02, Hiyori-n's birthday question.
What kind of question? What kind of question?
3, Hiyorin was the star of the show.
What kind of questions?
4. The "Let's give a present to Hiyori" corner. I'm really looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
05, Let's take a commemorative photo at the end of the session. There will be a screener time.
0.6, A final word from Hiyorin.
This is the lineup I would like to deliver today.This is the kind of lineup I would like to deliver today.
Ladies and gentlemen, I ask you all to please finish.
Best regards.
Me too.
Well, let's party together first.
Let's have a party.
I'll have one too.
Yes, you do.
Here, let's all sing together.
Maybe we should sing the Happy Birthday song.
Let's do something like that.
Okay, let's go.
Yes, let's go.
Please sing it, everyone.
Please do. Seino.
Happy Birthday to you
Happy Birthday Dear Hiroko
Finally Yay!
Happy Birthday to you
Happy Birthday to you.
Happy Birthday Queue you.
Happy birthday to you.
Congratulations.
Bye-bye.
Thank you very much.
Well, let's have a toast.
I want to make a toast.
Cheers.
It's got a straw on it, and it's cute.
YOLIN 22 years old
Yay.
Cheers.Cheers.
Is this a toast flag?
Cheers. - Cheers.
Yay.
Bye-bye.
You'd think it was me.
Yay.
Why, why, why?
Cheers.
Bon appétit.
You look a little thirsty.
Yes, it's good.
It's delicious.
It's good.
Delicious.
Very tasty.
Cold.
Delicious!
Yay!
Let's party!
Oops.
What do you think?
Looks delicious.
Sweets for everyone.
Thank you.
I think I'll have one too.
You too, Sook.
Curry.
I usually start with curry.
Strawberry or...
Lemon or cocaine?
It's delicious.
Which one do you want?
Sauk.Soak
It's delicious.
Can I open it?
Bon appétit.
What, talkie?
I've never seen one before.
Oh, yeah.
There's a lot of sandwiches.
Come on over if you guys want some.
I want you to have something to eat.
I have some.
No advertising.
I, about the other day.
I'm out.
Okay, this way.
Yes, matcha green tea sweets.
I always...
Matcha candy.
You've tasted matcha?
Lately.
Twenty-two times.
Um...
I had matcha cake.
I love it.
What matcha cake?
It's like...
It's like a green tea mousse.
With chestnuts on top.
With black ingredients.
Is it a Japanese dish?
Matcha cake
It was super matcha.
It's good!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Bon appétit.
Isn't that the green tea cake you made?
Isn't it?No?
Lisa Mari?
Didn't Rio used to make a matcha cake?
Yeah, I love matcha cakes.
Matcha cake?
Yeah, it's good.
It's delicious.
You make this.
Is this fun?
Yeah, it's good.
It's good, right?
It's delicious.
Is this what it's like with background music?
Today?
I'm having a great time today.
Are you waking me up that slow?
Always, always.
Always... always some kind of cake.
You want some cake?
I love cake. I love cake.
So there's no cake this time?
Yes, yes, yes.
Do you want a slice?
Let's have a slice of cake, too.
I want my cake now.
I'm just saying, we don't have a lot to buy.
I don't want to rush into anything.
I'll take it.
Oh, that looks so good. Oh, my God.
There's something on top.
Oh, it looks so good.
Looks delicious.
Oh, a piano.
It's so cute!
It says "Piano good.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm
Yay!
Yay!Got it!
I'm so happy
Yoo-hoo!
I did my best!
Yay!
Cute!
I wore this collar from last year's nativity goods today.
It's so cute.
The members wanted one too.
Really?
I hope the members will too.
It's so cute.
It's cute.
Cute.
I wore it today.
What today?
A little bit.
Is it on?
You're always wearing this.
Oh, yeah.
I'm not always on it.
This is it!
I miss it.
This, this, this.
Oh, it's like a delivery.
Let's eat.
Bon appétit.
No trouble.
No trouble at all.
How's it going?
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.Thank you.
This balloon.
The staff found it in Indonesia.
Oh, yeah.
Go get one.
There are a lot of Indivisual Croatians.
They put so many party goods in supermarkets and stuff.
I should have seen it.
I found some at the supermarket that I could dance to.
It's so cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
The colors are cute.
At the supermarket.
At the supermarket?
Isn't it a thing nowadays?
It's cute.
Is this it?
And you, too.
Haru...
Haru gave this to me.
Haru gave me this.
You're all I've got.
Right.
I have to give him a drink of water, too.
Squish, squish, squish.
So cute.
Anpanman
What an eric school.
Oh, it's cute
Cute.
Hari?
Soft
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha-haHa-ha-ha-ha!
I have a six-minute story to tell you.
I'd like to dance.
Last one.
Looks delicious.
Sounds good.
I've seen a lot of that.
Oh, yeah, that's good.
Easy to see.
Bon appétit!
Bon appétit.
Does anyone know what candy tastes like?
Oh, yeah, this is it.
Is it good?
It's the tea.
Oh, my God! I'm eating a whole cake.
I ate it!
Oh, my God!
Really?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I miss it. I saw a lot of it last year.
I know, I miss it.
I miss it.
Bon appétit.
Let's eat.
The grapes are fresh.
Delicious.
Delicious
Delicious!
Like grapes when you eat them
When you eat it
Delicious
I like grapes
For your sister
Ah!
Oh!Ahhh...
Good morning.
Delicious!
Hi, Haru.
Good luck on stage
Good luck on stage.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
You can do it.
You're so good!
Brawl's good.
Yeah, I like Bro.
I love Bro.
I love Braw.
I haven't bought any toys lately.
Lately.
I don't know.
I go to China Cut Value.
I don't go to Brauer Value.
Blow Value...
Brow value is
One, two, three, four
LOL!
LOL
You say
LOL!
To the tadpoles.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
October is good, isn't it?
To the taro.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Meeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!
I'm so hungry.I'm starving.
I was digging for ice cream.
I built a fire.
That's so cool.
On the spot production workers.
What's the product?
I made it out of act chokey.
You see this?
It's so cute!
He drew a picture for me.
It's a manual language.
He's so expressive.
He's cute.
When she was an idol...
Looks amazing.
Tends to do
Bangs
bangs
Cute.
Very cute
So cute!
Okay, everyone.
You can eat whatever you want.
OK, let's move on to the second corner of 2.
Let's see.... Hiyori's birthday question.
Yay!
So, this time, let's start with the X's.
Oh, yes.
I've asked for your questions on the "X" side,
Please read it.
Thank you very much.
Hi, Hi, Hi, Hi.
I'll return your question.
Oh!
LOL.
OK.
Here we go.
See ya.See you later.
It's kind of like a radio name. Normal.
It's from Mr. Pom.
What is Hiyori's favorite hairstyle?
If you don't mind, I'd also like to know each member's favorite haircut together with Hiyori's.
Oh, wow!
Well, first of all, my favorite hairstyle is, I guess, the stable twin-tail hairstyle.
Twintails are my favorite,
I always do it well.
It always looks good, and it has looked good for 7 years.
My voice is a little bit like that, if it doesn't look good, it becomes.
I don't have it.
I do it myself.
Twin-tails, twin-tails, curls? Or something,
Do you want to pull it down like a dumpling?
I prefer curly.
The lower part.
The lower part?
Half?
More like halfway down.
I like the bottom.
So you've seen too much.
That's right.
Kanami is
Dumpling or Cinderella's
Dumpling.
It looks great on you.
Kakun likes three-tiered buns.
Ehhhh...
Love yia yia que?
Oh!
Ooh.
Julian's like a sarella fan,
The hair, um..,
Frank?
Odoretto's?Odorette's?
Yes, yes, yes.
I just kind of roll it up, roll it up, like this,
I could take a picture with this horny thing,
I thought, "Oh, my God, I'm going to get it like this.
I thought it was pretty scary.
Really?
That, that...
A tray twin.
Yeah, I like it.
I like it.
I did it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
I like medium, and I like that do-straight.
Straight? Oh, really?
I'm soooo doing it.
Thank you.
I like it.
And Oharu looks good with her hair pulled back.
Much.
It makes you look even more beautiful.
I can tell.
You like it that way.
I like your hair pulled back in an elegant way.
I understand.
I like it.
Aki-chan, your twintails are cute.
Half-twins are cute, too.
Aki-chan, twintails.
Like, all twintails live.
They all have twin-tail love...
Exactly the same
On the last tour...
We all did 10.
That's good.That's good.
Come on, guys.
Take a step to the side.
Take a side step.
It's an important gig.
I can't try.
You're only going to give it one page
That's why
Subscribe to our channel.
Nice to meet you.
See you soon.
If you do the exact same haircut...
Oh, my God.
That would be fun.That's funny.
I want to do it once.
I want to feel it for a second.
Hey, guys.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
I'll live. I'll live.
But you're going to have to adapt to the three of us.
That's one way to do it. You know what I'm saying? You should put a canapin on it.
A little bit of a chain.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I can only call three people.
It's possible.
Next.
Aiko.
This is Aru-chan, Aru-chan.
Please tell me what's your favorite thing about me.
Ah! My boom!
My boom?
Boom?
I wonder what it is.I don't know.
But...
I haven't told you much.
I've recently started yoga.
Oh, wow! I thought you started yoga recently.
Oh, is that okay?
Early?
I've been wanting to try one myself.
Hiromi, I want to try one.
Did you do it often?
You're so asakakun.
Asakaku?
It's head yoga.
Head yoga? Is it hard?
No, it's not that hard.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Have you ever tried it?
I want to try it.
I definitely want to.
I'm looking forward to it.
But I don't know if I want to learn.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm going to try it with my best friend for the first time,
The combination of Nichiwa and yoga is interesting.
I've been looking at this service for a while.
She's not feeling well.
She's really sweating.
It's nice.
I'm going to continue.
This is from Maki-chan.
There were some fans who wanted to sing along with the specially selected songs.
Any other members?
I wonder what would be good.
What song?
I don't know.
But, you know, it doesn't have a lot of lines.
It's more than just lines.
Was there one?Was there?
Yes, ma'am.
Uh-huh.
But, I mean, is it love? I mean, is it love? Love? That's it.
I'm not sure if it's over yet.
It's cute.
No, but it's my favorite part.
The only other thing I'm asking for is...
Um, I was doing a fake.
Uh...
You've heard of it?
Yes, I've heard that.
I'm sure there's a lot of faking going on.
That's true.
I'd like to hear more about it.
But you know what?
Oh, shut up.
It's too loud.
Do you think the fakes will come?
No, I don't think we're getting any fakes.
Is that it?
The thingak?
Oh, yeah, the thingamajigs.
Oh, that's nice.
No matter how many times you quit, you're still going to be neat.
That's nice.
Translation.
I think I have about the next repiece.
I don't know where it is.
I'm so embarrassed.
What do you want?
I'm thinking.
Oh! It's Tagomi.
Can I buy a new parasol from Indonesia?
I want to hear it!
I, Hiyori Yoshikawa, got a new parasol.
Did you buy it? I bought it!
And I had a parasol that I bought once.And you know, I bought a parasol once.
You know, the part of the umbrella that snaps in place?
I originally used the button type.
You know, the button type.
But the new ones I bought...
But the new ones I bought were all new.
Oh, you got one of those? Really?
Yeah, they're out.
You know it.
I know, I know.
There's a button like this.
You don't have to hook it.
You have to do it, right?
I bought a new one.
And it didn't open and close in one motion.
It's a little awkward for everyday use.
It doesn't come off in one go.
I'll get you another one exactly like it, but I bought it in Indonesia.
You're going to collect it in Indonesia? We're collecting the exact same one.
That's why it was sold for real.
But the one that SHARE didn't use, we'll use the whole thing.
Okay, then.
You said you wanted one, right, Mom?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What? It's cute.
She really is.
I saw the look on your piano face when you were recruited.
What? What?
Don't cry.
It's funny.
I'll see you later with your puppy.
Take a picture to remember me by.
The princess's discarded umbrella.
I don't know... a plastic bottle... an unwanted plastic bottle...
She was throwing away her umbrella.
Obviously, she's throwing away her umbrella.
That's a nice story.Good memories.
Yeah.
That's funny.
Okay, next.
Well, then!
This is Mr. Bearded Bellhound.
Pio, can you handle fish?
I don't think I can handle fish.
My level is pretty low.
I see.
Like this.
Why do you think he looks like this?
Suzu-dog, Suzu-dog.
Can you make it?
I don't know.
It would be cool if you could handle it.
Sure is.
Catch something,
I'd like to try it,
I can't handle fish yet.
Is 22 a good age to raise fish?
Yes, it's good.
Yeah, it's cool.
It's cool.
I can go raise fish.
That's cool.
It's fast.
roll up, roll up, roll up
Oh, I got it.
I got it.
Oh, that's good.
It's from Yumi.
Do you have an undisclosed one-shot game?
Can you give me a pen for one of these?Can you give me one of these pens?
Then you can do it.
It's really good.
It's a normal one.
Wait, did you see it?
I saw it.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, don't listen to that noise.
Oh, there it is.
Ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten.
Simple.
Oh, I'll do it alone.
Cute, cute, cute, I want to eat with the members.
Oh, I want to do it.
Oh, it was already black.
Oh, it's finally here.
Success!
We're ready to have some fun this time!
That's strong.
That's great. That's great.
I'm the new Petahiro. New work.
Well, a little...
I'm just guessing.
Want to check it out?
You want to check?
Yes, go ahead. You can do it.
Yeah, you ready?
Yeah.
Yeah, come on.
What? What? What?
What?
Oh, peon, you're right.
Beep, beep, beep.
Beep.
I want to hear it now.
Oh, I got it.
You got it?
Yeah, a little bit. A little bit.Oh, hey, hey.
I'm 22 years old, and this is my first gag.
Even though it's small.
I just want to ask you something.
I don't know.
You know, I thought you might show up, so I was prepared.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
Four, comedian.
What?
Ha-ha-ha.
I knew you couldn't see me.
You're blind.
I love a good keeper.
Can you hold that for a second?
Okay, okay, okay.
All right, all right.
Let's see what you're tweeting about.
Yeah, the fan club.
I'll get you the image.
It's dead.
The lead actor is just now checking it out.
Let's go check it out.
I'm going!
He's back.
Okay, I'll go.
One-shot gag, here we go!
Earlier than the calendar.
And your shirt doesn't have cuffs.
Yes, I have a new one.
Shoe sleeves...
I'm telling the truth.
I'm telling you, I'm telling you.It's true.
It's true.
Yes, how about it?
Okay, I'll take it.
Mr. Yuri.
Kakegutty's over there.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
Thank you for the exit.
Interesting.
I'm standing next to someone.
What are you doing?
Oh, there it is. There it is.
You must be thrilled.
Yes, I'm very excited.
Thump, thump, thump, thump, thump.
Pounding, pounding, pounding.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I mean...
You saw a good one.
Well, go ahead and guess.
This is the last one.
Hey.
Oh, okay, I got a good question.
It's from 8Seven.
Good question.
Are you happy?
I'm happy.
I'm already happy.
Oh, my God.Oh, my God.
I've already done the last of the research.
I'm happy.
Mostly happy.
Happy.
Thank you very much.
So, this was Miyorin's corner to start the questions!
Yay!
I'm so nervous.
All right, then, the next question.
Show us your orange stick.
Everyone is happy.
Happy? Oh, good.
Everybody happy?
X
Oh, X
X.
Go on, then.
Oh, wow.
Kiarin is the star of the show!
(4) Dashi Moto no Corner
Yay!
Then, wow, wow, wow, wow!
First of all
Let's start with the first one.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh!
This way.
Let's start with
Let's start with the photos.
I'd like to
I'd like to unveil them to you.
This time, the 22-year-old witch goddess is here.
Well then.
She's cute.
Yes, she's got her stable twin-tail hair and color.Yes, I did color it with stable twin tails.
Cute.
How did you like it?
It's twisted.
Twisted.
It's cute.
It looks like it's painted on the coiffure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a little twisted.
It's so cute.
What do you think?
It's cute.
There's a soft, kind of light blue surrealistic version, and then there's a crisp-colored, kind of messy version.
and a light blue surrealistic version, and a crisp-colored, slightly messy version.
Cute!
There were soap bubbles, right?
Yes, I used soap bubbles.
I saw that one, too.
Oh, that's cute.
A different pattern.
Oh, Kakuyan, you're so cute.
You see that stone on his hand?
I'm holding it. It's cute.
I kind of scrunched up my hand,
You know, if you hold a stone, a tiny stone..,
I got 22 stones.
No, no, no, no, no.
I had other stones, too.
But, you know, I noticed that I had about 20 stones on my hand,
If I put two more, it would not be 22,
Oh, I see.
Yes, I put two on just right.
Cute.
Yes, it is.
One.
I want to kiss this.
What?What?
Did you find someone?
The one you want to kiss.
This one's expensive.
Number 413.
I'm sorry, I just want to see it.
He's cute.
Look at this.
He's kissing her.
He's making a "kiss me" face.
Oh, my God.
They were kissing.
We took a picture together, didn't we?
Yes, we did.
With the same looming.
I've got a video shot of the two of you.
All the time.
For Hitoka's birthday.
Ever since the costume came out.
We took a picture together.
When we took it.
So, you brought me and my shoes.
Oh, shoe size?
Timing.
I'll give it to you.
chiming
Super cute!
Cute!
It looks a little bit like soap bubbles.
I hope you all like it!
Please try to get a lot of them!
Yes!
Oh, this is
It's a Swin Jake.And it's Swin Jake.
Yes, Cheyenet.
Mr. Nail put a lot of thought into it.
Japanese small
The nails are so cute!
I love it!
To the right.
I'm sure.
Certainly.
To the right.
Which one do you have ready?
Two, three.
Hair.
And accessories.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, great, what a lot of stuff.
Yeah, get this one, I think it's a very detailed one if you look closely.
And it's got some backside rice and stuff on it, so...
Ooh.
I said, "Yes.
Cute.
Do you have any suggestions?
Do you have a recommendation?
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
Together.
Okay, I'd like to go to the group leader's entrance now.
Let's go!
Here's the gang leader's entrance.
There's a smart phone pad.
There's a phone pad, too.
Yes, he wrote his signature on some of these.
There's a real one, too.
It's a "Kanpatchi"?
A cute little handheld!
I see...
So cute!cute
cute
Cute.
Oh, you can make a video of this?
It's so cute.
Oh, yeah.
I'll let you guys film it.
Okay, first of all...
Okay, first of all, fresh photos.
So this is what we did with the mazsin treats.
I got quite a bit of mazsin, I got quite a bit of mazsin.
I've been wanting to do this, these days. All the time.
You know, the Instagram, they said they're coming to promote it.
So, it's got a QR on it,
I'd love it if you guys would make a team on your backs and stuff,
Then, Hiyori-chan will be there,
I'm Hiyori-chan, and you can follow me on Instagram.
Most of the Guardian staff will,
What do you think?
This one?
Oh, and this one.
Three?
Four?
This one, this one, this one, this one.
Oh, that's the one.
That's it.
Nice. Sunflowers.
Yes, sunflowers.
Sunflowers are nice.
Cute.
That's it. Hands with the sunflower letters.
Hands are cute.
I think it's this feeling
Um, sunflowers.
Sunflowers.
They were really cute.He was really cute.
Highly recommend!
One more to go!
rock, paper, scissors!
Hiyorin's
Half Series
Half
Always
In the story
I made it into a badge
I made it into a badge myself.
I'm trying to make use of the flip side too.
You know how you once created an Instagram account that only shows the other side of your work?
I like that.
I'm going to create such an account with my manager.
I won't use my name.
Sounds fun.
Repulsive.
Repulsive?
Your face.
I was wondering how you were doing.
But you've only been posting the new one for a week.
That's right.
So...
But next year, I'm going to make them all KABACHI antagonists.
As long as the antagonist is good.
I hope it's popular.
And the file.
Cute!
pop
Cute
Doesn't it look colorful?
It looks good on you.
It's so cute.
That's the first time anyone's ever said that to me.
It's cute.
It's cute.Cute.
Like this.
I'll go alone.
Cute.
Cute area too.
Really cute.
Yes, this one too Elia.
Cute.
Looks good in pink.
Her outfit is really cute too.
It was fashionable.
Cute.
At this point, what you've written is actually true.
I'm sorry, but...
I'm writing my text now
Ragged fish
Sara.
Good night
Short performance
Eh, cute, great!
I can do it horizontally and vertically
Cute.
Amazing.
Thank you
I was in a cool mood.
It sure did.
It's clear.
Cool.
I'm gonna be wrong.
Like this.
Store.
We have a lot lined up for the event.
Oh, great.
There's one out there.
Staff member's cell phoneStaff's cell phone
Yay.
You're so conscious.
Here's a cute memory.
I love it.
Take one out.
Oh, and the case.
What?
She's like, "Ha-ha-ha-ha!"
She's like, "I didn't see that coming!"
Daughter, "Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!"
Daughter, "Ha-ha-ha-ha!"
You'll do the same.
What's the exit?
It's all right.
You just did.
Exit.
I'm fine.
I'm available as a writer for that book.
By all means.
Please do it!
Please do.
OK.
And...
That one.
Which one was it?
We've made stateroom goods again this year!
I'm looking forward to it.
Last year, you made this.
Skew cake!
And this year it's this one!
Look at this!
Why is this here?
In that plush pouch!
Oh, it's so cute!
So cute!cute
the lily
I'm a little too fond of the little plushie.
I liked it a little too much.
I wanted to get a pouch with my face on it.
Oh, it's super cute!
So cute!
That's why
I want a frog headband
I put on a frog headband.
I'm wearing a frog headband with a frog design on the back.
And here, too. It's a flower.
It's so cute!
Isn't it cute?
So cute!
It's so cute!
Hey, maybe it's the little one.
Easy to use for a tiny girl.
And a charm, too.
Either
A set or B set.
Cute.
And the coloring.
It's so cute.
Cute.
Okay.
I don't know.
This much.
Looking forward to it.
Get the goodies!
I'm sure you'll love it.
Let's match them!
Yes, we do.
So cute.
It's cute.
I'd love to see some checks.
Oh, wow.
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
Cute.
Thank you very much.
Well, well, well.
Well, well, well. Oh!
Oh!
Well, I'd love to get some fresh photos.
We, Micho boy, and us, and all the goods you all saw, so...
Hiyori's entertainment corner
Ah! The last one is
Yes, sir!
That's it!
That's it, isn't it?
Oh, that one!
I sang 22 years old again this year! I tried it!
Yes!
I did it!
Why is that?
It doesn't make any sense at all.
Oh, I see.
Ha-ha-ha!
It's packed full.
I don't know.
They're all crooked.
Oh, did I take that?
Um..,
This Carinafe...
I got it!
Okay, then.
I hope you all enjoy listening to this while watching it.
I hope you enjoy listening to it!
Now, let's listen to today's newest work!
Feels good!
Elsa Elmina.
Here she is!
The smell of Fuzzy Navel makes me feel like I'm going somewhere.
I just want to drink up all those sweet, bitter, sad thoughts.
Hey.Hey.
I like that you're too serious.
It doesn't suit me.
What if I could stay by your side?
Yeah, no, that's what I'm thinking.
I've called your name so many times.
I've dreamed of a world of two people.
I've tried so many times to give up.
And then I'd come back and get you drunk.
Be me.
I smell of Pazienneble and I know I'm going somewhere
Every time I forgive you, my heart turns orange
I'm gonna fly away with you on the smell of Parsnips
I want to drink up all the sweet, sweet, sad feelings I have for you
It's so sad, I can't bear to see it end.
I know I don't have to tell you
But I still don't want to be beside you.
I don't think so.
ed.
Orange-tinted 5%.
True feelings dissolve in my memories
And they'll fade away
Before they're gone
The smell of Virgin Blue will take me somewhere
Every time I forgive, my heart turns orange
With the smell of mazy navel
I'll fly away with you
I'll drink up the sweet, bitter, sad feelings
I want to drink it all up
I'll fly away with you
With the smell of mazy navel
What a nice sound, isn't it?
Ha-ha-ha-ha
It's nice.
Yeah, it's kind of...
Twenty-two years old. A little mature.Twenty-two years old, a bit of an adult.
Twenty years old.
Two years after 20.
Orange juice to fuzzy navel.
I did it earlier. I drink a little bit of it, so I don't smell it.
That's true. See you later.
I think I'll do Fuzzy Nerve again.
But I'd also like to try a little shudder.
And if I say fuzzy nève in everyone's ears now, I'll be in the game.
It was like a white-eyed kapu, so I gave it a shot.
It was a little emo.
It's great, but it's so hard.
If you do it with a pulse, it's very, very hard.
I'm going to do it so much.
And that's what I'm going to do, and I'm going to tell the people who are involved in the
I hope you'll come to the class.
Please look at it a lot!
It's like aesthetics.
Yes, it was.
Cute.
It was totally beautiful.
And the letters were cute.
It was pretty.
The color was pretty, too.
It's orange.
It's cute.
This is totally unrelated, but...
Hatsune Miku
That's why I wanted to paint the orange side.
I ordered it, but it never arrived.
It didn't fit.
What's that? Huh?
Just a little bit.
It arrived the next day or so.
That's too bad.
You don't get those things, do you?
It's the timing.
Just a little bit more.Just a little bit more.
Yes, I mean.
After this, you know, after we're done with the delivery.
I'm sure it'll be up on YouTube.
I hope you'll watch it then too.
Please watch it a lot! Please do!
Yes, don't miss it!
Thank you very much!
Oh?
Oh!
Yes, let's continue.
That's what I'm looking forward to the most.
See you later.
Finally, everyone.
I made a mistake.
Oh, I made a mistake.
Last but not least...
Last of all
Ta-da!
Let's give Healin a present!
Yay!
I want a present!
Hey, guys, guys, look!
Look at this!
Oh!
Cool!
It's so cute!
Look at them!
Oh!
What?
Something just now,
Aki-chan's.
But, you know, she suddenly went to her room,
She said Raki was there.
Oh, no, he's going to find out.
It's okay.
Where do we start?Where do we start?
I'll make it easy.
Some of them are over.
Okay, hands over here.
Ready?
Ready.
Wait, what?
Okay.
Bikin' is so, so, so, so bad.
Eikle show
Oh, oh!
First one, first one...
Very, very, very bad
Oh, the first
Number two.
Three, four, five.
Okay, okay, okay, okay. Let's play.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Oh, but I know this place.
You do? Uh, something like...
I bought too much of that stuff that looks like honeysuckle and brought it with me.
Oh, that?
This place is so cute.
It's cute. Thank you.
I used to love their bags.
Oh, I see.
I'm so happy. It's been a long time. It's been a year.
I'm glad.
Yeah, it's been a while. I've been on a roll.
It's exhausting.
Yeah, you do. Every day.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
What's wrong?
You're wearing a lot of hats.
I don't know. He's just so excited.
Me, too.
It's just not what I had in mind.A little different in my opinion.
Cute!
So cute!
It's so cute!
It's so wide!
So cute!
I'm not sure why I bought these.
The socks are the same.
It's the same with the socks.
and display things that you can see.
over here.
Hit the water.
Unify them or something.
what's inside.
It's a light blue myroom.
Cute.
Before you know it
I feel like mijo
I'm so happy
Cute
Cute.
Thank you.
I'll watch you when I make it with this.
Okay, okay.
It's gonna be stiff.
It's so good. It's so good.
It's so good, I wish I had it out today.
I don't know.
You're super cute. That was pretty funny.
Thank you so much, guys.
Thank you very much.
It's rare.
Oh, my God.
The back of my hand.
The back of my hand.The back of my hand.
Oh, it's true.
Everyone's worried about you.
Julia, what's wrong?
Julia, you're not alone.
It's just like Julia.
Julia loves you.
Thank you.
Okay, now let's see what's next for the orphans.
Okay.
Oh, hi.
Your VTR has arrived.
Okay, let's start Oharu's VTR!
Happy 22nd birthday, Hiyori!
Happy Birthday!
Yes, that's right, I'm Oharu in super pink!
Is everyone enjoying the live streaming?
Hiyori, 22 years old, looking cute today? So cute!
So, here's what I got for Hiyori!
A cute mug with a strawberry pattern on it.
And below that... Oh, I didn't buy that one...
A mug, and a cute spoon with a strawberry on it.
A cute spoon with strawberries on it? Something like that.
I bought a set of spoons that look like muddler ken spoons!
I thought it was really cute and would look good on Hiyori.
I also bought them in the hope that Pio-chan would use them in her cooking!
And, a miracle has happened.
The last time I saw HITO-chan's
Aki-chan gave me a present with a similar design during Hito-chan's live broadcast,
I was talking about how I felt sympathy with Aki-chan for some reason,
If Hiyori-chan likes it and uses it, I would be very happy.
Yes! Well, Hiyori-chan and I have a lot in common in terms of singing,
We both love singing together,
I think we have a lot in common in terms of singing, and we also love singing together, and I think we are the ones who are praised for our singing by the main promoters,
I hope we can continue to work hard together and do our best in singing,
Hiyori's gags always make me laugh,
Hiyori's gags always make me laugh, so please let me learn a lot of laughter from you this year too!
I hope you have a wonderful year, too!So have a great year!
Happy New Year!
Thanks for the good morning!
You are so cute!
You're so cute!
If you received a message from Hiya-chan saying to use it for checkers...
Thank you!
It's so cute!
I'm going to fill Hiya's room with cute things.
Good morning. Thank you.
I'm so happy.
It's so cute.
It's so cute!
Like Autumn's tree.
Yeah.
It's so cute!
That's it.
Then, let's go give it to Hime-chan.
I'm the mom, but don't wear it.
Covered? I'll go.
Ta-da!
What?
Kanna!
It's big!
Where's my present?
Open it.
What?
Don't open it.
Kanna!
It's cute.
It sure is.
Can I ask you to wrap it for me?Oh, can I have it wrapped for a second?
No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
What?
I can't open it.
Let's open it.
Is this how you did it when you were a freebie?
Is this how it's supposed to be done?
Just a little bit more.
Let's put it like this.
It's kind of matchy-matchy, isn't it?
What?
It's cute.
What? It's cute.
Can I open this?
Can I open it?
It's so cute.
What? - What?
What?
Is it gonna rain soon?
It's gonna rain.
It's not going to rain soon.
Okay.
Let's go.
Se-no!
He's so cute.
How's he doing?
Poor little guy.
He's so cute.
Makes me feel better on a rainy day.
Hey.
Thank you so much.
I'm so happy to see you.
But if I'm in a crusa, I'm all alone.
I made a mistake.
I dressed like we're together again.
Wrong.I made a mistake.
I'm so happy now.
You're so cute.
That's so cute. Thank you.
At my age.
I wonder if Mr. Sucker's been playing Krusaa.
I'm so happy.
And there's two of them in the room.
They're so cute.
So cute.
Thank you so much.
They're adorable.
You'll never order from me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I forgot to run.
I'm forgetting, in case you're wondering.
Mr. Naka at the venue where you deliver it.
Let's say it's Mr. Yui's inside.
Thank you.
Cute.
Super cute.
Eh, it's really too cute already, everyone's majorly amazingly cute.
Okay, may I?
Okay, then.
Kananami.
Thank you very much.
Okay, Kanamin first.
What is it?
It's so big!
It's already grown a little.
Oh, it's grown so big!
What is it?
What does that mean?
I don't know.
What?
I don't think so.
But I think it's okay if we do it twice.
Oh, but I think it'll be okay if you take it.Oh, but I think it'll be okay if I bring it with me.
Yeah.
Awesome.
Wait a minute.
I like you too much.
I like it too much.
She likes it a lot.
I like you a lot.
Hey.
Ha-ha-ha.
Cute
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Hey.
Oh, my God.
Hey, guys.
Yui's favorite pineapple quit
Feet, these feet eyes
Everybody loves them!
I bought the one you eat a lot.
What?
What's that?
That's cute.
Oh, what's this?
Wow.
Suddenly there's something.
Hey, guys.
Guys.
The moment I put this on, it was just pew.
Oh, it's so cute.
This is it.
Yeah, there's a container in here.
I'm gonna open it.
Oh, my God.
Next year they'll all be like this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. They'll grow up.
They'll grow up.
We'll all be like thisWe're all in this together.
But can we use electronic batteries?
Yeah, they're all drawn.
This is what we're cooking with.
It's right here.
Currency machine?
Oh, that's cute.
Show bucket.
It's so cute.
It's not just cute.
There's so much more.
I can make with this.
Thank you.
Cooking buddy.
It's cute.
I'm gonna get my mom on it, so I can get my mom on it.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, he's so cute.
Thank you.
And the belly is cute, too.
Jack every time.
Thank you.
He's too cute.
I quit Pineapple.
You can use this for HIRO-chan cooking, too.
Hey, even the tableware will look cute.
You can put the recipe on it if you want.
I want to make something with the recipe.
That's fine.
Thank you.
It's much needed.
Looks delicious
Mino delicious!
You can take your mind off it.
There was a netfisher.
Yes, mooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
But you know, I already wrote this before I went to Indonesia.But you know, I already wrote that before I went to Indonesia.
I'm going to eat that once.
Change it back.
Yes, I changed it again.
Oh, and the last one...
It's not cute.
Not the cute kind.
But, you know, I'm confident.
I'm sure.
Wagyu beef.
Wow!
Wow, seriously?
Today. Beef.
Is that for real?
Yay!
Adorable.
Seriously?
But it's so good.
Meat. Steak.
Steak, steak, steak, steak.
It's easy to open.
It's a little cool.
Oh, thank you.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. But there's some cute people here.
I'll do that.
It's pretty good meat.
Thank you.
This is, um, kamago.
Oh, yes, kamago.
Wow!
They put the meat in as a boy.
I only have enough for one.
Really?
So extravagant!
Oh, my God.
Thank you, extravagant.Thank you Luxury.
Sorry I'm not prettier.
Thank you.
All of you. All of you.
Thank you
Everyone.
I'm so happy to give you this.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
No, no, no, no.
I'm so happy.
Well, let's continue.
I'm done with the Q&A section.
And finally, number 5.
Let's take a commemorative photo together.
Yay!
Let's take a picture.
Let's take a shot.
Oh, yeah.
Tull.
Tull here.
Let's take one look.
Uh, alone.
Yup.
Yay.
Twenty-two.
All 22 years old.
Oh, and I got a pink capin, too?
Eh?
Good night.
And here was time to help out on the REAL CRUSH!
Bye-bye.
So I'm here.
Well, I'll be backstage.
Bye-bye.
Bye, bye, bye.Bye-bye.
Very cute!
Psshaw.
Ah, hey, you caught up.
Now, same from today.
Same is a combination.
Now, Grandma, we're a duo now, too.
Yes, yes, yes.
The three of us until April.
Oh, wait a minute.
Same, same.
Excuse me.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry, I mean...
They're all taking good shots.
Well, let's go to bed.
Let's go to bed.
Thank you for watching
by A.K.
by H.
Kamizakura Posture Ribbit
Aimi Anyang
Look at You
It's called Kiyori Birthday TikTok Project.
From today until Saturday, August 19 from now until Saturday, August 19.
Use the specially selected song on TikTok
Upload your KiYori guess video!
Hashtag
hashtag
Kiyori's Special Selection
Hashtag specially selected Kiyorin Birthday
Don't forget to tag
And we'll draw 6 winners.
We will give away the cheki we just took!We will present you with the cheki photos we just took.
I hope you will all join us!
I hope you will join us!
I've already made a kid of and mensched me.
Thank you so much!
I'm really, really happy.
I'm so happy to see you all!
The 26th is the last day of the event!
Oh, 26th
26th.
This way.
It's extended
until the 26th of August.
We're on vacation, so...
Well, not yet.
I've got today's current screener and everything.
I'd love for you to use it or something.
It's the first time I've seen it.
Or a video or something.
That'd be great.
That's nice.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, picks and mains, everyone.
Okay, last one.
One last word from Peori.
Wow.
I'll do it again.
Well, I'll see you later. I can't tell you how much I've been thinking about you.
Well, I can't tell you how much I've been thinking about you.
Since the beginning of the semester...
Every year, every year...
I've had a lot of support from the main people and the members, of course.
I've had so much support...
Ah! Well, I guess this is the last time...
I've received a lot of congratulations...
This year, too.
I'm going to celebrate my 22nd year
I'd like to thank all the people who have devoted themselvesI'm so happy to see so many devoted Mainers
I am so happy to be able to celebrate with you.
I am filled with happiness.
You have all been involved in various activities over a period of time
I've been focusing on all the fun things you've been doing.
That's why I'm wondering if it's all right to be so happy all of a sudden.
I wonder if it's okay to be so happy.
On the contrary, there are things that make me feel uneasy.
But you only live once.
I think it's good to have fun all the time.
Let's really enjoy it.
Let's have fun.
I think the best way to live is to have fun.
Let's have fun, including those of you who are watching!
And you know, I've been writing about this for 22 years.
There are so many things I want to do.
I don't think we have enough time.
So even if you have an idea of what you want to do
I've put it off because I'm too busy.
From this year, I want to have the character to do things when I decide to do them, instead of putting them off.
I want to have the character to do it already.
From the point of view of what I want to do
I want to challenge various things again.
I'm happy as Tokisun.
I'm also very happy as Hime Yoshikawa.
Then, I'm going to try to grow up so that people will say I'm good at it.
I'll do my best so that people will say I'm even better.
I hope you will continue to support me.
I've received so much support this year.
I'd like to be more of a superstar, more of a superstar.
I think I can get support from all kinds of people.
I want to be that kind of person. I will do my best!
Let's do our best!
Yes, please advertise your feelings to Misemi's Hiyori Yoshikawa, too.
Please do. Thank you very much.
Me too?
Me too?Me too?
Special selection. I'm looking forward to it.
It'll be fun.
Fun?
It's fun.
Oh, yes.
What is it?
Well, Hiyori-n is all about messing around, isn't she?
Ah, what a surprise.
I wanted to thank everyone this year.
I've been playing gacha-gacha.
I don't usually play with colors, so I get it.
Okay.
Well, let's start with Aki-chan.
Okay, that's good.
Here you go.
Go ahead, create.
Oh!
Tone, I hope you enjoy it.
Kawawa will be sent off with the main campa kerack for the dance!
See you soon!
This one is for spring.
This is Shrina.
Ta-da!
All right, everyone.
Open it.
I'm going to have to work hard.
I'll do my best.
This time.
Um...
There it is.
Oh, you have a slip?
Yeah.
Are you with me? Let's go for it.
Let's do it.
I love it.
Braids.
I don't know. Let's do it.I'm going to make a decision.
We got on the same plane...
We're all in the same boat.
There were so many things...
Really...
What? This is so cute!
What was it, Akichan?
Aki-chan...
Oh! It's connected to that.
Yes, it's connected to that. I'll help you.
Ah! Aah! Sky-O!
It's Sky-O.
It's Sky-O!
Oshikiri.
Oshikiri ATM.
I'll do my best.
Osashi-ATM.
Oh, we'll do it together.
We're in this together.
And the flowers, too.
And flowers.
Seino!
Sorry, sorry.
Here are the flowers, too.
You're buying three?
Yeah.
Oh, well, I'll get...
But look at the two of us. We'll get the blue one.
Yeah, the blue one's perfect.
Aren't they cute?
It's cute.
I thought it would be a good idea to give it to a member.
Ha-ha-ha.
If you put it next to something like Axter...
You know, Chiliamus...
I see.
There's a lot of acsta corner.
You know, the members' axes and stuff.You know, like a member's axta.
It's cute.
I think of them as gacha-gacha.
Yeah, they're cute.
So cute!
You know, Sonny May...
They make cute houses.
I remember that.
Thank you very much.
This is a thank you from Twilley.
Thank you.
I'm glad you like it.
Thank you very much.
let's do it!
So, Ladies and Gentlemen
Thank you all for celebrating with us today!
Happy girl already!
Happy girl.
You happy?
I'm happy.
Yes, ma'am.
After this, we're going to continue with the live streaming of the fan club, so stay tuned for that.
It's at 6:00 p.m.
No, no, no.
From 6:00 p.m.
We're going to do a live streaming.
We're going to have a live streaming for the fan club.
There's more to come.
Yes!
And the stage will start at 6:00 p.m. after this.
Please enjoy it too!
The first day performance!
Yes, the first day performance!
Go, go, go!
Thanks for the present!
So, thank you all!So, thank you all!
Thank you very much!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
23!
Yeah!
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
undefined